I woke up in Tokyo
Tokyo, Tokyo
Everybody rock and roll
Lost in Tokyo
Shh
Listen
A-B-C-D-E-F-G
What you know ain't
What we see
Let's go
Ding-dong, ding-dong
I swear
I'm seeing King Kong
Head bouncing like a ping-pong
We poppin' out, it's on
Ding-dong, ding-dong
I swear
I'm seeing King Kong
"Good morning"
Are you ready for this?
One, it's good
Look at me-e-e
Ki-ki-key-ey-ey
My name is Ruka Kawai
I think
I might be dreaming
Ya
Looking for a fun time
Welcome everyone
Here BABYMON world
One, it's good
Look at me-e-e
Ki-ki-key-ey-ey
My name is Asa Enami
Brr
I woke up in Tokyo
Tokyo, Tokyo
I'm like, oh, oh, oh
Let's go
I woke up in Tokyo
Yeah
Tokyo, Tokyo
I woke up in Tokyo
This be loco-co
Loco
Thank you
Rock and roll
Everybody rock and roll
Let's doing something with me
Lost in Tokyo
Say
I woke up
In Tokyo
Asa
Yum, yum, yum
Mmm
We gon' run and gun
Ayy
Come and get you some
Come get it
Get 'em one by one
Pew, pew
We pulling up
Boo-hoo
The level up
Goku
Kamehameha
Ayy
Yakiniku in pajamas
Ohh
Yamaguchi go bananas
You know that
No, you don't want no drama
Cross fingers area expansion
I woke up in Tokyo
Tokyo, Tokyo
I'm like, oh, oh, oh
Hey
I woke up in Tokyo
Tokyo, Tokyo
Yeah
I woke up in Tokyo
This be loco-co
Loco
Thank you
Ohh
Rock and roll
Everybody rock and roll
Let's doing something with me
Lost in Tokyo
Hands up
I woke up in Tokyo
In Tokyo
Thank you
s2